

## Camilo Restrepo

Front-end Developer

My name is Camilo Restrepo and I am a Front-End Developer and UX/UI Designer with more than 2 years of experience. I have worked on various projects ranging from designing and developing custom websites to maintaining and updating existing sites. My skill set includes modern frontend technologies like React, Angular, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Figma design skills as well as working with agile methodologies such as Lean and Design Thinking. I am known for my ability to work well in teams and my focus on user-friendly and visually appealing design. My portfolio shows my experience and quality in web development and web design. I am dedicated to learning, continue to grow in my career, and am excited to apply my skills to challenging new projects.

## **Experience**

2019 - Present

Front-end Developer Monitored technical aspects of the front-end delivery for several projects.

2019 - 2020

**Director of business** development

Collaborate with creative and development teams on the execution of ideas.

2008 - Present

**Technical support for** computers

Repair, maintenaince and upgrade for hardware and software for computers.

## Education

2023

Zero To Mastery Academy Successfully completed the course Complete React Developer in 2023 (w/ Redux, Hooks, GraphQL) as taught by Andrei Neagoie, Yihua Zhang, Zero To Mastery.

2015 - Present

**Antioquia University** Bachelor's Degree electronics engineering in Antioquia University

2009 - 2010

## Compuedu

Technique in computer Science in Compuedu institute



